[opening theme playing]
NEWTOPIA
[Jae-yoon] I got this. [panting]
I got this!
Let's go! Here I come!
Yeah!
Young-joo!
[thuds]
[groans, grunts]
[panting]
[hissing]
I did it.
Hell yeah!
[snarling]
[sighs]
Huh?
Sergeant Ahn Sung-gyu.
PLATOON 005
[grunts]
[blows]
[snarls]
- [thuds]
- [gasps]
[panting]
[growls]
- [gunfire]
- [In-ho] They're swarming the entrance!
- [Arron] Push it down!
- [In-ho] See you next fall!
[snarls]
Holy fuck.
[pants]
[panting]
[man 1] Stop running!
[man 2] Hey! Stop.
- [man 3] We better not lose her.
- [gasps]
- [man 2] Hey! Stop!
- [grunting]
[man 1] What are you doing?
Come here already.
[grunts]
[man 2] You motherfucker.
I'm gonna kill you.
- [man 1] I saw something!
- [man 2] Stop right there.
[men laugh]
[man 2] Hey. Hey!
Get over here, huh?
I'll just cut your head off.
[man 1] I'm tired of chasing you.
Come here!
Get over here or it'll be even worse! Huh?
[grunts]
- [man 2] Darling!
- [whimpering]
Oh, shit!
- [man 1] I see you.
- [gasping]
[men chuckle]
Look! Right over there.
- We found her.
- She's mine. [chuckles]
- Ahh...
- Oh, where are you?
[laughs]
[whimpering]
[man 1] Ugh, fuck this. I give up!
Wow girl! You're really good at hiding!
- [man 2] You'll never go home!
- [man 3] Come here!
All right! Let's go home.
[laughs]
[man 2] Yeah, let's just go home already.
[grunts]
- [pants]
- [man 1] Hey!
[man 2] Huh?
- Let's just go home! Come on!
- [man 3] Let's go! [laughs]
[panting]
[man 1] There you are! Bitch!
- Get over here!
- [screams]
- [man 3] Hurry!
- [man 1] She's getting away! Grab her!
[man 3] Little shit! [groans]
I'm gonna fucking
tear your hair off, you bitch!
[Young-joo screams]
[man 3] You fucking bitch!
[laughter]
[whimpering]
[man 2] Man, I'm tired of this shit.
[gasps]
[snarling]
[man 2] Stop! Hey!
It's the last car. Get her.
[gasps]
- [snarling]
- [straining]
- [Young-man] Hey! Watch out!
- [grunting]
- [Gye-young] Miss Soo-jeong!
- [Soo-jeong screams]
[straining]
I need to get to the window!
[screaming]
[grunts]
[Gye-young] Stand back!
- [In-ho] Arron Park!
- [Arron] Private!
Keep pushing!
[screams]
- We need to push more down!
- Oh, my good god!
[both exclaiming]
- [Jae-yoon] You guys!
- [In-ho] He didn't die!
- [Jae-yoon] Over here!
- [Arron] Lee Jae-yoon!
[Jae-yoon] Ra In-ho, Arron Park!
- I'm still alive.
- Hell yeah!
[laughs]
Is everyone else okay?
- [laughs]
- You guys!
Lee Jae-yoon! He's down there! Alive!
- Get it together! They're attacking!
- [screams]
- [snarls]
[screaming]
[laughter]
Yeah!
Aww... Oh, my God.
[pants]
[radio beeps]
[Jae-yoon] All right everyone, listen up.
Here's our solution.
Zip-line.
Think of it like zip-lining, okay?
Now take off your vests,
and use them to ride down here.
- Steady.
- Slowly.
[Jae-yoon] First, grab hold of the main
cable attached to the gondola
and fasten it tightly to the window frame.
[panting]
- There you go.
- [Jae-yoon] Once it's fastened,
I'll make sure to detach
the other end of the cable here.
[grunts]
Then I'll fasten it to the back
of the truck across the street.
The truck is far enough from the building
to create tension on the cable.
This should allow all of you
to get down here safely from up there.
Also, we have to slow you all down
before reaching the bottom.
Luckily the truck we're tying the cable to
has a bunch of mattresses in it.
I'll build a landing pad around the truck,
that'll cushion the impact
and get you to safety.
I know it's scary, but this is the only
option you have.
Yes!
Come on!
Hurry!
If the combat vest
can't hold the weight, it'll tear.
- [Jae-yoon] Hurry up!
- This is too risky.
- I think we should--
- Hey, idiot.
Why don't you open that door
if you think this is scary?
[Jae-yoon] Hurry up!
- [Kyung-sik] What a pathetic loser.
- Uh...
[whirring]
[Jae-yoon] Hwang Kyung-sik!
You're doing great!
Yes! Like that! Great! That's it!
That's it! Careful!
Well done, man!
[sighs] That idiot.
[Jae-yoon] It's safe! Come on down!
- Hey.
- I don't like this.
[whimpering]
[Jae-yoon] You can do this!
- [whimpers] Shit!
- [Jae-yoon] Ra In-ho!
- I just--
- [Jae-yoon] You got this!
This jump is way too high! [cries]
In-ho, there's no time for this.
[whimpers, pants]
- [Jae-yoon] Jump! Come on! Let's go!
- Just hold on! Give me a second.
- Hold on tight.
- Ohh.
[screaming]
There he goes.
- [Jae-yoon] You're doing it!
- [screams]
[Jae-yoon] Ra In-ho!
You got it! You got this! Go!
[In-ho whimpering]
[laughter]
Private First Class Lee,
it's so good to see you again!
I thought I would never
see you alive again! I'm so happy!
[laughter]
What is this, a romantic comedy? Jesus.
Damn! That bitch is kind of fast.
Hey! You've reached the end, huh?
Hey, open the door.
Oh shit! Is her head under there?
[laughs]
- Yes.
- Idiot! Open the fucking door!
- [gasps]
- Oh, shit!
- [snarling]
- [men screaming]
[man 1] Get off me!
[man 3] You fucking assholes!
Ugh! Stay away!
[screaming]
[panting]
[men screaming]
[woman] Hey you! Over here.
Come on, over here! Hurry up!
This way. Come on, this way.
Hurry!
- [Jae-yoon] Next one!
- Let's do this, let's go!
- Yeah, let's go.
- Miss Soo-jeong.
- [Jae-yoon] Hurry up!
- Yeah.
Ready, Soo-jeong?
- [In-ho] Who's next?
- Manager.
- [In-ho] You guys can do this!
- Are you okay?
[Jae-yoon] Corporal Kwak Gye-young!
- [Arron] Yeah!
- [chuckles]
- [Gye-young] You're up. I got your back.
- [Soo-jeong] Okay. [sighs] All right.
[In-ho] Kyung-sik. You did incredible!
- Uh... Hold on.
- [Jae-yoon] What's taking so long?
- Just a second.
- [In-ho] They have to hurry!
- [Jae-yoon] Hurry up!
- Don't worry about anything.
I'll be right here.
Everything will be okay.
I've got your back. You can trust me.
Hey, dude...
Why are you acting
so corny all of a sudden?
Oh!
That was a little too much, huh?
- You got this, Okay, Soo-jeong.
- Jesus...
- [Jae-yoon] They coming?
- [sighs] Okay. You win!
- I'm trusting you.
- [In-ho] Just believe in yourself!
- Yep!
- [In-ho] You got this.
- [sighs]
- [In-ho] I think she's ready!
[exclaims]
[Jae-yoon] Come on! Go!
- Yes!
- Come on!
[Jae-yoon] That's it! That's great!
Just like that! A little more!
[In-ho] Keep going!
- [exclaims] Woah!
- Woah!
- You okay?
- [exclaims] I did it!
- Woah! Are you okay? Yeah!
- I actually did it!
- You did it.
- I did it!
- You did it!
- Kwak Gye-young!
- You should be a general!
- [cheering]
- [Gye-young] I'll be right down Soo-jeong!
- [In-ho] You got this!
Ah, fuck. Whoa!
You go down first. I'm gonna
be right behind you, Arron Park.
- [laughter]
- Let's do this.
- How are you going to get down? [exclaims]
- Don't worry, I'll see you there!
[Jae-yoon] You got this! Come on!
[all cheering]
[laughter]
- One more left!
- Sergeant Kim!
Hurry up! It's not that bad!
Hold up. Whose is this?
- It-- It-- It's Sergeant Kim's.
- Huh? Huh?
[Gye-young] Sergeant Kim.
Sergeant Kim?
- How are you getting down?
- [Gye-young] You're the last one, hurry!
[Kyung-sik] What are you doing?
- Let's go! Hell to the yeah!
- Hey, hey. Hey!
Wait a minute.
Oh my god, what an idiot.
[sighs]
I think it's over for me.
- Huh? What?
- Huh?
What?
I think...
You guys have to keep going.
But without me.
[sighs]
- [Jae-yoon] Sergeant Kim!
- [In-ho] Wait!
Hey, Sergeant Kim!
Just get down here. Yeah?
We'll figure something out.
- Hey, booze!
- [In-ho] Oh. Alcohol...
[Arron] Drink some booze
and you'll be fine!
Alcohol's the only reason I'm still human.
- It's true...
- [Arron] We'll figure it out together!
- [beeps]
- [Young-man] Booze?
That doesn't make any sense.
Oh, wait. Hold on!
Actually Arron Park
just keeps drinking alcohol
and he hasn't mutated yet!
Sergeant please drink some alcohol! Yeah?
- [beeps]
- [Young-man] You know,
[chuckles] as crazy as that sounds
I believe you.
But I feel like [sighs]
it's already a little too late for me.
Make sure...
Everyone survives.
This is my final order as acting
squad commander.
- Hey...
- No! Wait, wait!
Sergeant Kim! Wait, please!
[beep]
Young-man...
[sighs]
[woman] Come. It's safe.
Be careful. Watch your step.
Be quiet!
This way.
It's over here! Hurry!
[Young-joo gasps]
Are these zombies or people?
[woman] Given the amount of blood
on the floor, definitely human.
They were killed
by the thugs that chased you.
So heartbreaking.
- Are you all right?
- What?
Oh... I'm not sure.
Follow me.
Don't worry. It's safe here, I promise.
We'll wait here, so that you can rest up
and head to the station.
- Any luck, Ra In-ho?
- [In-ho] Still looking sir!
[Soo-jeong] Oh, come on! [grunts]
[In-ho] Gosh! Nothing here.
[sighs, gasps]
Huh?
[beeps]
- [In-ho] I found them!
- [Gye-young] You found them?
- [Soo-jeong] Really? Amazing!
- [Jae-yoon] Great work! Thank god!
[grunts]
Oh, I'll take it.
- Let's go. Start it, hurry.
- Wait!
Kyung-sik. He's not here yet.
Oh...
He just...
Ran off by himself somewhere.
And you only told us about it right now?
[sighs] Shit.
Let's get going. Drive to Suseo Station.
Yeah, let's go.
[snarling]
[car alarms blaring]
[thud]
[snarling]
[sighs]
[whimpers]
[Young-man] This kid got an award
at training camp.
- Whoa!
- He's a rockstar!
Hey Hyung-bae, what's this guys name?
- Private Hwang Kyung-sik
- Wow.
Corporal Kim, your son's an ace too?
That's not fair.
With the luck we've got
we'll end up with washed-up geezers
for our sons.
Huh? Please don't jinx me,
that's uncalled for!
Kyung-sik you said?
Private Hwang Kyung-sik!
This is my son now.
Nobody messes with him.
- Ah-huh!
- Okay, then.
Now we're family.
Private Hwang Kyung-sik!
Got it, right!
Private Hwang Kyung-sik.
Thanks for the meal, sir!
Eat up now, son.
[groans, blows]
All right, I've finished.
Yeah, here.
- Private Hwang Kyung-Sik.
- They're perfect sir.
Ah, no need to say thank you.
A father has to make sure his son
is presentable on his first leave.
And those, I made sure to get
the sharpest creases ever.
- [chuckles]
- Oh, also...
Here. Take it.
- No, it's okay.
- Please, take it.
Your birthday is coming up.
Treat yourself to a good dinner.
[chuckles] You don't have to.
Just take it already.
- My arm's tired. You little shit.
- I can't take it, sir.
[sighs]
I really appreciate it, sir.
Thank you, Dad.
[whimpering]
[gunshot]
[sighs]
[breathing heavily]
Shit.
[gasps]
[panting]
- [phone trilling]
- Come on. Come on, come on.
- [Young-joo's mom] Hello? Young-joo?
- [exclaims] Mom!
- [Young-joo's mom] My Young-joo!
- Are you okay?
- [Young-joo's mom] Where are you?
- You're still alive!
[Young-joo's mom sobbing]
Are you okay, sweetie?
Are you okay?
- Where are you?
- At a train station.
- I need to get out of here!
- [Young-joo's mom] Young-joo!
Are you safe there?
You're not in danger, right?
I'm hiding deep
in the Express Bus Terminal.
I'm safe, don't worry!
[Young-joo's mom] Why didn't you
go where Jae-yoon is?
It's a really long story.
But I was rescued by a lady who works
at the train station so I'm safe.
Just promise that you'll stay home.
[Young-joo's mom] What are you
doing there?
I... I went looking for Jae-yoon but...
Things got really crazy
and I ended up here.
[Young-joo's mom] Are you all right?
How are you going to come home?
Everything's okay, really.
In the morning I'll head to Suseo Station
to come and get you.
- [Young-joo's mom] Where? Young-joo?
- [woman shushes]
[Young-joo's mom] Young-joo!
[Young-joo's mom] Is everything okay?
Hey mom! I need to get going now.
Just... please stay home.
[Young-joo's mom] Okay.
- Don't worry about me. Yeah.
- [Young-joo's mom] Be careful.
- So sorry. Well...
- Mmm-hmm. No worries. Really.
The phone is working now.
You should be able to call home.
I'm okay.
Maybe later.
That's sweet, though.
SEOUL METRO
PARK EUN-CHAE
- Park Eun-chae.
- Yeah?
Um, you just saved my life.
I wanna make sure
I never forget your name.
SEOUL METRO
PARK EUN-CHAE
Yeah.
They call me,
Park Eun-chae.
- Park Eun-chae.
- And your name?
I am Kang Young-joo.
[Eun-chae] Nice to meet you, Young-joo.
[engine whirring]
[snarling]
[In-ho] What's that? It's a dead end!
- Turn around! U-turn! U--
- [Gye-young] Wait... Hold on!
Ah, shit. This way's blocked too.
Sorry, guys. I should have told you
but I'm a bad driver.
- Hold up!
- Huh?
Maybe I should just stay here.
- [all] What?
- I think that...
My time has run out.
- Huh.
- [Soo-jeong] What? Manager...
- You're sober?
- [Soo-jeong] What?
- [sniffs] Aww, shit!
- [Gye-young] What are you gonna do?
Alcohol.
We need alcohol now!
There has to be, a bar
or convenience store.
[Jae-yoon] Chinese restaurant.
JIN PALACE
Huh? Th... There has to be alcohol.
- [Soo-jeong] Oh!
- Oh!
- [In-ho] Get out! hurry!
- Come on, guys!
[Soo-jeong] Let's go.
[Arron] Booze. Booze!
[gasps]
[Jae-yoon] Arron Park...
Are you okay?
[sighs]
I think we're safe here.
[phone trilling]
Young-joo, please.
Answer me.
[clicks, beeping]
[sighs] Shit!
- [clatter]
- [gasps]
Soo-jeong! [gasps]
It's pork! Look sweet and sour!
- Hell, yeah!
- [exclaims]
- Oh! Gye-Young!
- Have some!
- [sighs]
- [chuckles]
- Mmm...
- Wow! Oh!
- So good. Mmm!
- That sauce?
- Yeah!
- Like it?
- Yes, I do.
- So do I. Heck yes.
- [chuckles]
- Try it!
- This counts as our Chinese dinner date.
[chuckles]
Seriously?
Are you messing with me?
Everyone right now just needs
to relax and decompress.
- Hmm!
- My stress reliever is humor.
So is food.
Ah!
Okay.
Then, you are now,
officially allowed to crack jokes
and cheer up all of us.
- Got it?
- Got it!
[chuckles]
- Oh?
- Jjamppong broth.
Hell, yeah! This looks delicious!
Huh?
Hmm?
What's this?
[gasps] Oh, my God!
Mmm. Settle down! Seriously!
- Miss Soo-Jeong. Is this your Instagram?
- Huh?
Why are you calling me Miss Soo-jeong?
You're actually older.
- Wow! Wow!
- Just say Soo-jeong.
- I'm sorry!
- Mmm-hmm.
Soo-jeong!
[both laugh]
You really are a bit of a weirdo,
aren't you?
Thank you so much!
[gulping]
[exhales]
[sighs]
I'm going drink myself to death.
ENDURE
HANGOVER REMEDY
[Arron] Huh?
- [clicks]
- [grunts]
[grunts] Huh?
You cannot allow yourself
to give into despair, Arron Park.
You cannot die on us.
Never, ever give up,
no matter what happens!
Okay.
Appreciate it, Private.
I'm still in this fight.
[chuckles]
I'm giving you some ginseng for energy.
Energy-juice.
- We're gonna become invincible!
- Screw it.
[beeps, clacks]
[dial tone]
[phone trilling]
Ah!
I'll be home soon.
- [Young-joo's mom] Young-joo?
- Hello?
- [Young-joo's mom] Huh?
- Oh, Mrs. Kang!
[Young-joo's mom] Oh! [gasps]
Hello, Mrs. Kang.
It's Jae-yoon, I'm Young-joo's...
[Young-joo's mom] Jae-yoon!
Is everything all right?
Are you safe where you are?
Yes. I'm doing all right, are you safe?
[Young-joo's mom] I'm okay.
I locked myself at home.
Young-joo just called me.
She's looking for you!
She said she's hiding with a transit
worker at the Express Bus Terminal.
I've tried calling back
but the lines are disconnected!
- Express Bus Terminal? You sure?
- [Young-joo's mom] Yes.
She said she would rest up for the night
and try to come get me in the morning.
[gasping]
It just feels too dangerous. Jae-yoon!
- Can you go get her?
- Young-joo...
- [Young-joo's mom] Jae-yoon?
- Yes, ma'am.
Don't worry, I'll go to her right away.
I promise you.
And whatever you do, don't go outside.
Just swear to me that no matter what,
you'll stay inside.
[Young-joo's mom] All right.
Please be very careful Jae-yoon.
It's so dangerous!
No need to worry yourself.
I've trained, you know?
- Don't you worry, all right?
- [Young-joo's mom] Okay. Good.
Oh, oh, good.
Wait for us and we'll come get you.
- [Young-joo's mom] All right. I'll wait.
- [sighs]
- [In-ho] Huh?
- A kid.
- [Arron] Huh?
[In-ho] There's a kid!
We need to bring--
[sighs]
[sobbing]
[Eun-chae] It seems
like things have calmed down.
Do you think we should get going now?
- Right now?
- Mmm-hmm.
All we need to do is open the shutter.
There's a control room
not far down the hallway.
If we can connect
the subway's emergency power line,
we should be able to open it.
We always keep a backup generator
for emergencies.
- I'm gonna go and do it.
- Oh! I'll go with you.
Young-joo.
Do you ever wonder why pilots, never eat
the same meal as the rest of the crew?
Huh?
I'm saying it's safer
if we don't go together.
I'm gonna head to the control room,
and open the shutter.
I'll activate all the breakers.
That should get the lights turned on.
Do you see that shutter?
[Young-joo] Yes.
When that goes up, mission accomplished.
Understand?
I need something I can use as a weapon.
Um... Let's see...
This'll work.
Wait here for a bit.
I'll be right back, okay.
[breathing heavily]
[coughs]
Get in here.
What are you standing there for?
You know your family is waiting for you.
I'm clear about what needs to happen next.
I need to rescue Young-joo.
It's been a true honor.
I've only made it this far,
thanks to all of you.
Now, it's time for us to go home.
Let's go get our loved ones.
We need to protect them.
[engine whirring]
JIN PALACE
[panting]
Shit.
[clanging]
[whimpering]
- [clanging]
- [grunting]
[muffled snarls]
- [thud]
- [gasps]
Ugh! Zombie head!
[clatters]
- [snarls]
- [gasps]
[Jae-yoon] Ugh, damn it.
Young-joo.
Kang Young-joo.
Ugh, shit.
[snarling]
[gasps] No, no, no!
No! Stop!
Back off! Get away! [grunting]
[groans]
[grunting]
Young-joo!
Kang Young-joo!
Can you hear me Young-joo?
[gasps]
Jae-yoon!
Lee Jae-yoon!
Young-joo!
[Young-joo] Lee Jae-yoon!
[gasps]
- [Jae-yoon] Young-joo!
- [gasps]
Jae-yoon!
I'm over here!
Young-joo!
[exclaims]
[panting]
[grunts]
I'm coming! Jae-yoon!
Jae-yoon!
- Young-joo-- Whoa!
- [gunshots]
Young-joo!
- [snarls]
- [gunshots]
Young-joo.
[snarling]
[grunting]
- [thuds]
- [groans]
Young-joo.
[snarls]
[gunshot]
[grunting]
Fuck you! Argh!
Assholes! Motherfuckers!
- [grunting]
- [snarling]
Oh, God!
[screams]
Jae-yoon!
[panting]
- [gunshots]
- [Jae-yoon screaming]
[gasps]
Jae-yoon!
Jae-yoon! Jae-yoon!
Young-joo.
[gasps] Jae-yoon!
Ah!
Young-joo.
[gasps]
Jae-yoon!
Young-joo!
[gasps]
[snarling]
Young... [snarling]
[gasps]
[snarls]
- [gunshot]
- [screams]
Young-joo.
[sighs]
Jae-yoon, it's you!
Young-joo.
[Young-joo whimpers]
Jae-yoon.
Young-joo.
It's okay now.
What the hell too you so long?
I must look disgusting.
You look beautiful.
- Blood really compliments your eyes.
- [chuckles]
Jae-yoon! [cries]
What took you so long? [crying]
Sorry, Young-joo.
I'm sorry I took so long.
You're safe. Huh?
You're okay.
Come here!
- Stay close to me. Got it?
- Yeah.
Understood. Ah, shit.
[gasps]
- Shit. Wait.
- [gasps]
Hold on!
I have this.
- What's that?
- A weapon.
- [gunshots]
- [screams]
[thuds]
But how?
[grunting]
[gunshot]
[Gye-young] Cover me!
Huh? Huh?
[all grunting]
[gunshots]
[Arron] It's done? All clear?
- [In-ho] Yes!
- [Soo-jeong] Oh!
[all sighing]
[all panting]
[Jae-yoon] Hey...
What are you guys doing here?
The gang decided to aid in the rescue.
There's no way this private
was gonna survive without us.
But your families...
Thankfully, they're all safe.
From now on, we move together.
No ifs, ands or buts about it.
Our odds of survival are higher
if we stay close.
We will rescue each other's families!
Looks like it's our best choice.
Uh...
Hey, who are these people?
They're my friends.
Hey.
Oh, jeez, you're covered in blood.
[Arron] All right, everything's packed.
Let's get going.
- Young-joo.
- Huh?
- I think it's probably time to go.
- Let's wait.
Eun-chae still hasn't come back yet.
Any minute now.
Okay. We're done doing recon.
Coast is clear.
- Was she out on her own?
- [Young-joo] Yeah.
She said she'd open the shutters
and be back.
Food is packed. Everything is good to go.
So...
Uh... How did you get here?
I was rescued by a woman.
I followed her down here.
Her name was Park Eun-chae.
So this Eun-chae personally asked you
to wait for her to lift the shutter?
Yeah, that's right.
How long have those bodies
been laying out in front of the cafe?
- Ah... They were...
- What?
Already laying there when we arrived.
Ah... Gotcha.
Hey, uh, Lee Jae-yoon, can I have a word?
Huh?
Seriously, what's going on?
SEOUL METRO
PARK EUN-CHAE
Park Eun-ch--
[gasps]
Wait...
- Did they just kill her?
- Impossible.
They've been decomposing for quite
a few hours. There's no doubt.
- So this means...
- [Young-joo] What's going on?
[both] Oh! Oh...
- [Young-joo] What's wrong?
- Ah! No, no.
Nothing.
Oh, right.
I didn't tell you that I saw a woman
in a metro uniform running out.
- What?
- And the name tag said Park Eun-chae!
- What's going on?
- Oh, really?
- [Arron] Everything okay?
- Seriously?
Gosh, idiot. Now you're telling us?
- [Young-joo] She survived!
- I'm sorry.
- Young-joo. Come with me.
- [Young-joo] Huh?
- Let's get out of here. Come on.
- [Young-joo] Okay.
- [Soo-jeong] Let's go.
- [Gye-young] All right.
- [In-ho] This way.
- [Gye-young] Do we know which way?
[In-ho] We have to go left.
[Jae-yoon] Ra In-ho,
you better know the way.
[Eun-chae] They call me Park Eun-chae.
[Young-joo gasps]
[muffled snarls]
You can't even imagine
everything that I've been through.
[sighs] It feels like a dream.
TO: JAE-YOON - STAY SAFE
YOON JONG-SHIN
But this was real.
Here! It's a present for you.
What is this?
- Where did you get it.
- [chuckles]
It's even got a signature.
And look here. Signed in person.
What? Stop messing with me,
why would you do that?
I'm not making it up.
Your name is right here, Jae-yoon!
Stop playing. How could you meet
Yoon Jong-Shin in all this chaos?
Actually he's back at the metro station.
I even caught his live performance.
[radio announcer speaking]
- Seriously?
- I wouldn't lie to you.
- Yoon Jong-shin kicks ass.
- You seriously got his autograph?
- I swear!
- Seriously though?
[all chattering]
[radio announcer] Due to the emergency,
officials have ordered a lockdown of Seoul
and all surrounding cities.
Anyone in these areas
must immediately proceed to Incheon Port,
where ferries are transporting evacuees
to a secure facility on Jeju Island.
Please disregard previous instructions
directing you to Suseo Station.
I repeat, do not proceed to Suseo station.
[Soo-jeong] The Han River. It's beautiful!
- [Gye-young] How about a break?
- [Soo-jeong] Should we?
- [Young-joo] Let's stop.
- [Jae-yoon] Wanna get out?
- [Arron] I need to stretch.
- [In-ho] Fresh air.
[Jae-yoon] Hey wait. Hey Young-joo!
Careful getting out!
[all sigh]
- [Young-joo] Don't worry, I'm fine.
- [In-ho] I needed this.
[Soo-jeong] It's incredible.
- [Gye-young] Beautiful.
- [In-ho] Oh my...
- [Gye-young] Soo-jeong. Soo-jeong?
- [Soo-jeong] Huh? [chuckles]
[Arron] Man, it's a shit show here too.
What a mess.
[In-ho] Huh?
[exhales]
We're not...
- Huh?
- Ending things, are we?
There's no reason for us to break up.
[Gye-young] I'm hungry.
There's no graduation or military
to worry about.
- [Gye-young] Think we can have our date?
- [Soo-jeong] Stop joking!
That's true.
See...
Even if things never return to normal,
it'll always be the two of us.
No matter what happens,
I will...
Always be there to take care of you.
Actually...
Maybe I'll take care of us.
Please.
- [explosion]
- [Soo-jeong gasps]
- [whooshes]
- [all exclaim]
- Huh?
- That scared me.
[explosions]
Might as well get moving.
- Huh?
- This is not over yet!
[Jae-yoon] Damn it!
- Come on.
- [Gye-young] Soo-jeong, let's go.
- [Young-joo] Jae-yoon, hurry.
- [In-ho] Hurry and get in!
- [Jae-yoon] Be careful!
- [Gye-young] Come on! Watch out!
[Young-joo] Hurry! Get in the car! Now!
[all exclaiming]
- Go!
- Oh, my God!
- Let's get out now!
- Floor it!
- Let's Go!
- To In-ho's house!
- [In-ho] That sounds good!
- [Arron] Let's go!
[In-ho] Ha-yul, daddy's coming!
[closing song playing]